love my wife you guys
16 years next month isn't that awesome
16 years
we fight though from time to time
all couples fight every couple's had
that one fight right you know that fight
where you stop and you think to yourself
whoa
did i just say that
i might as well say everything now
those jeans make you look fat
i know i can't believe my wife said that
i can't that was so
that was wildly inappropriate
not right at all that was not right
we love each other we've had to do some
strange things together like one time we
had to go to a couple's wedding shower
anyone out there been to a couple's
wedding shower
you have
you're just moving your arm
well you picked the perfect time for it
sir
couple's wedding show yeah
i had to go to a couple's wedding shower
with my wife and we love each other very
much 16 years a beautiful child we love
each other very much but
we were fighting when we had to go to
that couple's wedding shower and that is
a tough thing because you're going to
this event this party together to
celebrate two people in love celebrating
their lives together and at the time my
wife and i had to pretend that we liked
each other
it was hard so we're at the front door
it's like
that door opens hey
[Laughter]
so excited for you
and they made us play games at the
couple's wedding shower they make you do
this they make you play games they made
us play the newlywed game
you know you know the game where you
have to guess what your spouse says and
you leave the room and try to match it
up this is a disaster when you're
fighting
can i just say that
because what you're fighting about is
just gonna passively aggressively bubble
to the surface
and make things weird for everybody
so my wife and i are fighting we're
playing the newly wed game and i kid you
night this is the very first question
they asked us the first question they
asked us is what was the last thing you
and your spouse fought about
i know
i couldn't believe it
so i just tried to keep it light right
i'm like
leaving the toilet seat up
and then they asked my wife what was the
last thing you and your spouse thought
about and she said how completely
unfulfilled i am oh my god
we laugh like this all the time these
are the jokes when you're in love as
long as we are we make jokes like this
this is fun that's what love is it's
joking and laughing
and we do we laugh a lot we love a lot
my wife's very very proud of me it's a
good time in my life i mentioned that
i've lost that weight
i weighed 335 pounds
and my wife's excited about that you
think my wife's excited my wife is
excited sometimes she tells me she feels
like she's married to somebody else
i know that sounds weird but it's a
compliment isn't it
it sounds weird so i've started doing
this thing from time to time when it's
just the two of us you know sometimes
i'll get up leave the room shove a
pillow under my shirt run back in and
you know what's going on here
what are you doing with ron howard's
brother
[Music]